Religious Broadcasters Interview Collection
Religious Broadcasters Interview Collection
- Interviews
  - Stevens, Betty and Paul, Dr. interviewed by Dr. David Clark, Fort Worth, Texas (tape 1 of 2), 26 Jun 2000; rel_broad_int_117; Betacam: SP; running time 60:00 (Box 6)
    Interview taken place at Southern Baptist Communication Center Studios of Family Net
  - Stevens, Betty and Paul, Dr. interviewed by Dr. David Clark, Fort Worth, Texas (tape 2 of 2), 26 Jun 2000; rel_broad_int_118; Betacam: SP; running time 60:00 (Box 6)
  - Sweeney, Terrance A., Dr. (tape 1 of 1), 24 May 2001; rel_broad_int_119; interview has no transcript; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 6)
  - Thoman, Elizabeth, Sister, interviewed by David Marc, Los Angeles, California (tape 1 of 1), 9 Aug 2000; rel_broad_int_120; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 6)
  - Wellingham, Edward (tape 1 of 2), 11 May 2001; rel_broad_int_121; interview has no transcript; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 6)
  - Wellingham, Edward (tape 2 of 2), 11 May 2001; rel_broad_int_122; interview has no transcript; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 6)
- Masters
  Masters are in mini-DV format. There are mo masters for Bane, Humbard, Rose, Schuller, or Stevens.
  - Armstrong, Richard N. interviewed by David Marc, Tappan, New York (tape 1 of 3), 17 May 2000; rel_broad_int_123; MiniDV; running time 63:00 (Box 4)
  - Armstrong, Richard N. interviewed by David Marc, Tappan, New York (tape 2 of 3), 17 May 2000; rel_broad_int_124; MiniDV; running time 63:00 (Box 4)
  - Armstrong, Richard N. interviewed by David Marc, Tappan, New York (tape 3 of 3), 17 May 2000; rel_broad_int_125; MiniDV; running time 63:00 (Box 4)
  - Bakker, Jim interviewed by David Marc, Vernon, Florida (tape 1 of 4), 12 Dec 2000; rel_broad_int_126; MiniDV; running time 63:00 (Box 4)
  - Bakker, Jim interviewed by David Marc, Vernon, Florida (tape 2 of 4), 12 Dec 2000; rel_broad_int_127; MiniDV; running time 63:00 (Box 4)
  - Bakker, Jim interviewed by David Marc, Vernon, Florida (tape 3 of 4), 12 Dec 2000; rel_broad_int_128; MiniDV; running time 63:00 (Box 4)
  - Bakker, Jim interviewed by David Marc, Vernon, Florida (tape 4 of 4), 12 Dec 2000; rel_broad_int_129; MiniDV; running time 63:00 (Box 4)
  - Carmichael, Ralph interviewed by Stephen O'Leary (tape 1 of 3), [no date]; rel_broad_int_130; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 4)
  - Carmichael, Ralph interviewed by Stephen O'Leary (tape 2 of 3), [no date]; rel_broad_int_131; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 4)
  - Carmichael, Ralph interviewed by Stephen O'Leary (tape 3 of 3), [no date]; rel_broad_int_132; MiniDV; running time 30:00 (Box 4)
  - Clarke, David E., Ph.D. interviewed by David Marc (tape 1 of 2), 26 Jun 2000; rel_broad_int_133; label has misspelled name "David Clarck"; MiniDV; running time 63:00 (Box 4)
  - Clarke, David E., Ph.D. interviewed by David Marc (tape 1 of 2), 26 Jun 2000; rel_broad_int_134; label has misspelled name "David Clarck"; MiniDV; running time 63:00 (Box 4)
  - Cooke, Phil interviewed by David Marc, Burbank, California (tape 1 of 3), 7 Aug 2000; rel_broad_int_135; MiniDV; running time 63:00 (Box 4)
  - Cooke, Phil interviewed by David Marc, Burbank, California (tape 2 of 3), 7 Aug 2000; rel_broad_int_136; MiniDV; running time 63:00 (Box 4)
  - Cooke, Phil interviewed by David Marc, Burbank, California (tape 3 of 3), 7 Aug 2000; rel_broad_int_137; MiniDV; running time 63:00 (Box 4)
  - Crouch, Paul F., Sr. interviewed by Stephen O'Leary (tape 1 of 2), 8 Jul 2000; rel_broad_int_138; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 4)
  - Crouch, Paul F., Sr. interviewed by Stephen O'Leary (tape 2 of 2), 8 Jul 2000; rel_broad_int_139; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 4)
  - Cunin, Baruch Shlomo, Rabbi interviewed by Michael Epstein, Los Angeles, California (tape 1 of 3), 13 Dec 2000; rel_broad_int_140; label has misspelled name "Rabbi Boruch Shlomo Cunin"; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 4)
  - Cunin, Baruch Shlomo, Rabbi interviewed by Michael Epstein, Los Angeles, California (tape 2 of 3), 13 Dec 2000; rel_broad_int_141; label has misspelled name "Rabbi Boruch Shlomo Cunin"; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 4)
  - Cunin, Baruch Shlomo, Rabbi interviewed by Michael Epstein, Los Angeles, California (tape 3 of 3), 13 Dec 2000; rel_broad_int_142; label has misspelled name "Rabbi Boruch Shlomo Cunin"; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 4)
  - Cutié, Alberto, Father [Albert], Rector of St. Benedict's Church interviewed by Mort Silverstein, Miami Beach, Florida (tape 1 of 2), 17 Jan 2000; rel_broad_int_143; interview has transcript; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 4)
  - Cutié, Alberto, Father [Albert], Rector of St. Benedict's Church interviewed by Mort Silverstein, Miami Beach, Florida (tape 2 of 2), 17 Jan 2000; rel_broad_int_144; interview has transcript; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 4)
  - Ferm, Lois, Dr., Coordinator at the Billy Graham Library, interviewed by David Marc (tape 1 of 3), 11 May 2000; rel_broad_int_145; MiniDV; running time 63:00 (Box 4)
  - Ferm, Lois, Dr., Coordinator at the Billy Graham Library, interviewed by David Marc (tape 2 of 3), 11 May 2000; rel_broad_int_146; MiniDV; running time 63:00 (Box 4)
  - Ferm, Lois, Dr., Coordinator at the Billy Graham Library, interviewed by David Marc (tape 3 of 3), 11 May 2000; rel_broad_int_147; MiniDV; running time 63:00 (Box 4)
  - Fore, William F., Rev., Director of the Broadcasting and Film Commission of the National Council of Churches, interviewed by David Marc (tape 1 of 3), 8 Aug 2000; rel_broad_int_148; MiniDV; running time 63:00 (Box 4)
  - Fore, William F., Rev., Director of the Broadcasting and Film Commission of the National Council of Churches, interviewed by David Marc (tape 2 of 3), 8 Aug 2000; rel_broad_int_149; MiniDV; running time 63:00 (Box 4)
  - Fore, William F., Rev., Director of the Broadcasting and Film Commission of the National Council of Churches, interviewed by David Marc (tape 3 of 3), 8 Aug 2000; rel_broad_int_150; MiniDV; running time 63:00 (Box 4)
  - Goodman, Jane interviewed by David Marc, Canyon Lake, Texas (tape 1 of 2), 17 Mar 2000; rel_broad_int_151; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 4)
  - Goodman, Jane interviewed by David Marc, Canyon Lake, Texas (tape 2 of 2), 17 Mar 2000; rel_broad_int_152; MiniDV; running time 65:00 (Box 4)
  - Ilott, Pamela interviewed by David Marc, Canyon Lake, Texas (tape 1 of 3), 17 Mar 2000; rel_broad_int_153; MiniDV; running time 63:00 (Box 4)
  - Ilott, Pamela interviewed by David Marc, Canyon Lake, Texas (tape 2 of 3), 17 Mar 2000; rel_broad_int_154; MiniDV; running time 63:00 (Box 4)
  - Ilott, Pamela interviewed by David Marc, Canyon Lake, Texas (tape 3 of 3), 17 Mar 2000; rel_broad_int_155; MiniDV; running time 63:00 (Box 4)
  - Khankan, Al-Haaj Ghazi Y., executive director of Council on American-Islamic Relations and Director of interfaith affairs at the Islamic Center of Long Island, NY interviewed by Mort Silverstein, Islamic Center of Long Island (tape 1 of 2), 1 Dec 2000; rel_broad_int_156; MiniDV; running time 90:00 (Box 4)
  - Khankan, Al-Haaj Ghazi Y., executive director of Council on American-Islamic Relations and Director of interfaith affairs at the Islamic Center of Long Island, NY interviewed by Mort Silverstein, Islamic Center of Long Island (tape 2 of 2), 1 Dec 2000; rel_broad_int_157; MiniDV; running time 90:00 (Box 4)
  - Kinchlow, Ben, Reverend, interviewed by David Marc (tape 1 of 2), 15 Feb 2000; rel_broad_int_158; MiniDV; running time 63:00 (Box 4)
  - Kinchlow, Ben, Reverend, interviewed by David Marc (tape 2 of 2), 15 Feb 2000; rel_broad_int_159; MiniDV; running time 63:00 (Box 4)
  - McClurken, D. W. (Bill), Reverend interviewed by David Marc, Tape A (tape 1 of 3), 30 Mar 2001; rel_broad_int_160; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 4)
  - McClurken, D. W. (Bill), Reverend interviewed by David Marc, Tape B (tape 2 of 3), 30 Mar 2001; rel_broad_int_161; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 4)
  - McClurken, D. W. (Bill), Reverend interviewed by David Marc, Tape C (tape 3 of 3), 30 Mar 2001; rel_broad_int_162; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 4)
  - McSweeney, Thomas, Monsignor, interviewed by David Marc, The Christopher's Building, NYC (tape 1 of 3), 31 Mar 2000; rel_broad_int_163; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 4)
  - McSweeney, Thomas, Monsignor, interviewed by David Marc, The Christopher's Building, NYC (tape 2 of 3), 31 Mar 2000; rel_broad_int_164; MiniDV; running time 60 (Box 4)
  - McSweeney, Thomas, Monsignor, interviewed by David Marc, The Christopher's Building, NYC (tape 3 of 3), 31 Mar 2000; rel_broad_int_165; MiniDV; running time 60 (Box 4)
  - Pomeroy, David, Reverend, interviewed by David Marc, Spring Valley, New York, Tape A (tape 1 of 3), 29 Mar 2001; rel_broad_int_166; interview has no transcript; MiniDV; running time 60 (Box 4)
  - Pomeroy, David, Reverend, interviewed by David Marc, Spring Valley, New York, Tape B (tape 2 of 3), 29 Mar 2001; rel_broad_int_167; interview has no transcript; MiniDV; running time 60 (Box 4)
  - Pomeroy, David, Reverend, interviewed by David Marc, Spring Valley, New York, Tape C (tape 3 of 3), 29 Mar 2001; rel_broad_int_168; interview has no transcript; MiniDV; running time 60 (Box 4)
  - Price, Nelson, Pastor interviewed by David Marc (tape 1 of 3), 15 Jun 2000; rel_broad_int_169; MiniDV; running time 60 (Box 4)
  - Price, Nelson, Pastor interviewed by David Marc (tape 2 of 3), 15 Jun 2000; rel_broad_int_170; MiniDV; running time 60 (Box 4)
  - Price, Nelson, Pastor interviewed by David Marc (tape 3 of 3), 15 Jun 2000; rel_broad_int_171; MiniDV; running time 60 (Box 4)
  - Robertson, Pat "Marion Gordon" interview by David Marc, Christian Broadcasting Network (tape 1 of 2), 16 Feb 2000; rel_broad_int_172; MiniDV; running time 60 (Box 4)
  - Robertson, Pat "Marion Gordon" interview by David Marc, Christian Broadcasting Network (tape 2 of 2), 16 Feb 2000; rel_broad_int_173; MiniDV; running time 45 (Box 4)
  - Spong, John, Bishop interviewed by David Marc, Marristown, New Jersey (tape 1 of 3), 11 Sep 2000; rel_broad_int_174; MiniDV; running time 60 (Box 4)
  - Spong, John, Bishop interviewed by David Marc, Marristown, New Jersey (tape 3 of 3), 11 Sep 2000; rel_broad_int_175; outside, paper label is for rel_broad_int_176; MiniDV; running time 60 (Box 4)
  - Spong, John, Bishop interviewed by David Marc, Marristown, New Jersey (tape 2 of 3), 11 Sep 2000; rel_broad_int_176; outside, paper label is for rel_broad_int_175; MiniDV; running time 60 (Box 4)
  - Sweeney, Terrance A., Dr. (tape 1 of 2), 24 May 2001; rel_broad_int_177; interview has no transcript; MiniDV (Box 4)
  - Sweeney, Terrance A., Dr. (tape 2 of 2), 24 May 2001; rel_broad_int_178; interview has no transcript; MiniDV (Box 4)
  - Thoman, Elizabeth, Sister, interviewed by David Marc, Los Angeles, California (tape 1 of 2), 9 Aug 2000; rel_broad_int_179; MiniDV; running time 60 (Box 4)
  - Thoman, Elizabeth, Sister, interviewed by David Marc, Los Angeles, California (tape 2 of 2), 9 Aug 2000; rel_broad_int_180; MiniDV; running time 60 (Box 4)
  - Wellingham, Edward (tape 1 of 3), 11 May 2001; rel_broad_int_181; interview has no transcript; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 4)
  - Wellingham, Edward (tape 2 of 3), 11 May 2001; rel_broad_int_182; interview has no transcript; MiniDV (Box 4)
  - Wellingham, Edward (tape 3 of 3), 11 May 2001; rel_broad_int_183; interview has no transcript; MiniDV (Box 4)
- Audio versions
  Audio-only versions of video interviews, on audiocassette. Complete set.
  - Armstrong, Richard N. interviewed by David Marc (tape 1 of 2), 17 May 2000; rel_broad_int_184; audio versions of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120:00 (Box 4)
  - Armstrong, Richard N. interviewed by David Marc (tape 2 of 2), 17 May 2000; rel_broad_int_185; audio versions of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120:00 (Box 4)
  - Bakker, Jim interviewed by David Marc (tape 1 of 2), 12 Dec 2000; rel_broad_int_186; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Bakker, Jim interviewed by David Marc (tape 2 of 2), 12 Dec 2000; rel_broad_int_187; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Bane, Will, United Methodist Communications, interviewed by David Marc, Nashville, Tennessee (tape 1 of 2), 24 Oct 2000; rel_broad_int_188; interview has no transcript; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Bane, Will, United Methodist Communications, interviewed by David Marc, Nashville, Tennessee (tape 2 of 2), 24 Oct 2000; rel_broad_int_189; interview has no transcript; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Carmichael, Ralph interviewed by Stephen O'Leary (tape 1 of 2), [no date]; rel_broad_int_190; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Carmichael, Ralph interviewed by Stephen O'Leary (tape 2 of 2), [no date]; rel_broad_int_191; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Clarke, David E., Ph.D. interviewed by David Marc (tape 1 of 1), 26 Jun 2000; rel_broad_int_192; label has misspelled name "David Clark"; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Cooke, Phil interviewed by David Marc, Burbank, California (tape 1 of 2), 7 Aug 2000; rel_broad_int_193; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Cooke, Phil interviewed by David Marc, Burbank, California (tape 2 of 2), 7 Aug 2000; rel_broad_int_194; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Crouch, Paul F., Sr. interviewed by Stephen O'Leary (tape 1 of 1), 8 Jul 2000; rel_broad_int_195; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Cunin, Baruch Shlomo, Rabbi interviewed by Michael Epstein, Los Angeles, California (tape 1 of 2), 13 Dec 2000; rel_broad_int_196; label has misspelled name "Rabbi Boruch Shlomo Cunin"; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Cunin, Baruch Shlomo, Rabbi interviewed by Michael Epstein, Los Angeles, California (tape 2 of 2), 13 Dec 2000; rel_broad_int_197; label has misspelled name "Rabbi Boruch Shlomo Cunin"; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Cutié, Alberto, Father [Albert], Rector of St. Benedict's Church, interviewed by Mort Silverstein, Miami Beach, FL (tape 1 of 1), 17 Jan 2000; rel_broad_int_198; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Ferm, Lois, Dr., Coordinator at the Billy Graham Library, interviewed by David Marc (tape 1 of 2), 11 May 2000; rel_broad_int_199; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Ferm, Lois, Dr., Coordinator at the Billy Graham Library, interviewed by David Marc (tape 2 of 2), 11 May 2000; rel_broad_int_200; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Fore, William F., Rev., Director of the Broadcasting and Film Commission of the National Council of Churches, interviewed by David Marc (tape 1 of 2), 8 Aug 2000; rel_broad_int_201; audio verson of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Fore, William F., Rev., Director of the Broadcasting and Film Commission of the National Council of Churches, interviewed by David Marc (tape 2 of 2), 8 Aug 2000; rel_broad_int_202; audio verson of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Goodman, Jane interviewed by David Marc, Canyon Lake, TX, Tape 1 (tape 1 of 2), 17 Mar 2000; rel_broad_int_203; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Goodman, Jane interviewed by David Marc, Canyon Lake, TX, Tape 1 (tape 2 of 2), 17 Mar 2000; rel_broad_int_204; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Humbard, Rex, Reverend interviewed by David Marc, Pigeon Forge, Tennessee (tape 1 of 2), 29 Aug 2000; rel_broad_int_205; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Humbard, Rex, Reverend interviewed by David Marc, Pigeon Forge, Tennessee (tape 2 of 2), 29 Aug 2000; rel_broad_int_206; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Ilott, Pamela interviewed by David Marc, Canyon Lake, Texas (tape 3), 17 Mar 2000; rel_broad_int_207; audio version of video interview; Mini-cassette; running time 60 (Box 4)
  - Ilott, Pamela interviewed by David Marc, Canyon Lake, Texas (tape 1 of 2), 17 Mar 2000; rel_broad_int_208; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Ilott, Pamela interviewed by David Marc, Canyon Lake, Texas (tape 2 of 2), 17 Mar 2000; rel_broad_int_209; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Khankan, Al-Haaj Ghazi Y., executive director of Council on American-Islamic Relations and Director of interfaith affairs at the Islamic Center of Long Island, NY interviewed by Mort Silverstein, Islamic Center of Long Island (tape 1 of 2), 1 Dec 2000; rel_broad_int_210; audio version to video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Khankan, Al-Haaj Ghazi Y., executive director of Council on American-Islamic Relations and Director of interfaith affairs at the Islamic Center of Long Island, NY interviewed by Mort Silverstein, Islamic Center of Long Island (tape 2 of 2), 1 Dec 2000; rel_broad_int_211; audio version to video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Kinchlow, Ben, Reverend, interviewed by David Marc (tape 1 of 1), 15 Feb 2000; rel_broad_int_212; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - McClurken, D. W. (Bill), Reverend interviewed by David Marc (tape 1 of 2), 30 Mar 2001; rel_broad_int_213; audio version of video interview; handwritten on front: "tape 1 of 2; Side 1; Side 2 on separate tape"; handwritten on back: "side 3"; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - McClurken, D. W. (Bill), Reverend interviewed by David Marc (tape 2 of 2), 30 Mar 2001; rel_broad_int_214; audio version of video interview; handwritten on front: "part 2"; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - McSweeney, Thomas, Monsignor, interviewed by David Marc, The Christopher's Building, NYC (tape 1 of 2), 31 Mar 2000; rel_broad_int_215; interview has interview; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - McSweeney, Thomas, Monsignor, interviewed by David Marc, The Christopher's Building, NYC (tape 2 of 2), 31 Mar 2000; rel_broad_int_216; interview has interview; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Moss, Jim, Dr., interviewed by David Marc, Pigeon Forge, Tennessee (tape 1 of 2), 16 Feb 2001; rel_broad_int_217; interview has no transcript; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Moss, Jim, Dr., interviewed by David Marc, Pigeon Forge, Tennessee (tape 2 of 2), 16 Feb 2001; rel_broad_int_218; interview has no transcript; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Pomeroy, David, Reverend, interviewed by David Marc, Spring Valley, New York (tape 1 of 2), 30 Mar 2001; rel_broad_int_219; interview has no transcript; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Pomeroy, David, Reverend, interviewed by David Marc, Spring Valley, New York (tape 2 of 2), 30 Mar 2001; rel_broad_int_220; interview has no transcript; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Price, Nelson, Pastor interviewed by David Marc (tape 1 of 2), 15 Jun 2000; rel_broad_int_221; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Price, Nelson, Pastor interviewed by David Marc (tape 2 of 2), 15 Jun 2000; rel_broad_int_222; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Robertson, Pat "Marion Gordon" interview by David Marc, Christian Broadcasting Network (tape 1 of 1), 16 Feb 2000; rel_broad_int_223; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Rose, Jerry, Total Living Network, interview by David Marc, Chicago, Ilinois (tape 1 of 2), 9 Nov 2000; rel_broad_int_224; interview has no transcript; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Rose, Jerry, Total Living Network, interview by David Marc, Chicago, Ilinois (tape 2 of 2), 9 Nov 2000; rel_broad_int_225; interview has no transcript; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Schuller, Robert H., Dr., interviewed by Dr. Michael Epstein (tape 1 of 1), 4 Oct 2000; rel_broad_int_226; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Spong, John, Bishop interviewed by David Marc, Marristown, New Jersey (tape 1 of 2), 11 Sep 2000; rel_broad_int_227; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Spong, John, Bishop interviewed by David Marc, Marristown, New Jersey (tape 2 of 2), 11 Sep 2000; rel_broad_int_228; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Sweeney, Terrance A., Dr. (tape 1 of 1), 24 May 2001; rel_broad_int_229; interview has no transcript; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Stevens, Betty and Paul, Dr., interviewed by Dr. David Clark, Southern Baptist Communication Center, Fort Worth, Texas (tape 1 of 1), 26 Jun 2000; rel_broad_int_230; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Thoman, Elizabeth, Sister, interviewed by David Marc, Los Angeles, California (tape 1 of 1), 9 Aug 2000; rel_broad_int_231; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
  - Wellingham, Edward (tape 1 of 2), 11 May 2001; rel_broad_int_232; interview has no transcript; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120:00 (Box 4)
  - Wellingham, Edward (tape 2 of 2), 11 May 2001; rel_broad_int_233; interview has no transcript; audio version of video interview; Audio cassette; running time 120 (Box 4)
- Transcripts
  Transcripts created by Cyrill White, Conference Reporting Service. Each transcript includes a cover sheet with full information (name, date, media format, etc.). There are no transcripts for Bane, McClurken, Moss, Pomeroy, Rose, Sweeney, Wellingham.
  - Armstrong, Richard N. (Box 7)
  - Bakker, Jim (Box 7)
  - Carmichael, Ralph (Box 7)
  - Clarke, David E. (Box 7)
  - Cooke, Phil (Box 7)
  - Crouch, Paul F., Sr. (Box 7)
  - Cunin, Baruch Shlomo (Box 7)
  - Cutié, Alberto (Box 7)
  - Ferm, Lois (Box 7)
  - Fore, William F. (Box 7)
  - Goodman, Jane (Box 7)
  - Humbard, Rex (Box 7)
  - Ilott, Pamela (Box 7)
  - Khankan, Al-Haaj Ghazi Y. (Box 7)
  - Kinchlow, Ben (Box 7)
  - McSweeney, Thomas (Box 7)
  - Price, Nelson (Box 7)
  - Robertson, Pat (Box 8)
  - Schuller, Robert H. (Box 8)
  - Spong, John (Box 8)
  - Stevens, Betty and Paul (Box 8)
  - Thoman, Elizabeth (Box 8)